From the dating website.
(Emily:)Your friend emailed me
because you were afraid to,
(Emily:)then you tracked me down
and acted like a lunatic?
(Raj:)Yes, Rajesh Koothrappali.
Look, I just...
I wanted to say I'm sorry.
(Raj:)You were, like, the coolest person
I ever found online,
(Raj:)and I got really nervous
and I just blew it.
(Emily:)Don't worry about it.
(Emily:)And if it makes you feel any better,
(Emily:)you're not the weirdest guy
I've met off the Internet.
(Raj:)Well, give me a chance,
you don't even know me.
(Emily:)All right, here's your chance.
What? Really?
(Raj:)Thank you.
(Raj:)Fate has given me
a rare second chance,
(Raj:)and I swear to Vishnu
I'm not gonna blow it.
(Raj:)Or normal words
followed by a charming smile.
(Sheldon:)First there was PlayStation,
aka PS1,
(Sheldon:)then PS2, PS3 and now PS4.